[{"answer": "You know, it is so heart-breaking, Piers.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 25, "question": "What do we know about the person that perpetrated this hideous crime?", "qSentId": 24}, {"answer": "Well, obviously it's been a horrific day in the greater Danbury area and particularly the town of Newtown.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "What can you do?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "There are vigils scheduled throughout this community, Newtown, throughout weekend.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "Did you know if there plans for more vigils tomorrow?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "I received a call from the school system from the superintendent saying that there was a shooting in Newtown, but didn't say it was a school, that the schools were on lockdown.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "When was the first you heard about this and how did you hear?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "When you got there, obviously scenes of complete chaos, how quickly was it that you realized your daughter was safe?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "Not really.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "Can you hear?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "I don't know if you can ever predict something like that would happen.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "Is this something you could have predicted he would one day flip and do something as monstrous as this?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "I always saw him alone when he was walking through the school or when he was sitting at the table, or sitting on the bus.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "Was he sociable?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "He was really quiet.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "How would you describe his personality?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "I mean, I knew her because we lived in the neighborhood.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "Did you know his family, his mother in particular?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "I don't know when they got divorced.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "Were you aware of that having a big impact on him?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "It was devastating.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "What was your immediate reaction when you discovered it was this person you knew?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "Probably middle school.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "When was the last time you spoke to Adam Lanza?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "You know, working on a lot of these cases, there a number of different causes that can be divided into two broad categories.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "What is the possible background to what is going on here?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "Look, there is no question that firearms play a role.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "Are people like this as likely to carry out what they end up doing, these atrocities, if they didn't have easy access to firearms?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "I think the first thing is helping the parents.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "Where do you start with trying to counsel young children when this kind of appalling thing happens?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "You know, I don't have a crystal ball and I haven't diagnosed or assessed him.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "Why he would then, having killed his mother, go to the school and do what he did?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "I'd like to endorse that also.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "Frank?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Well, there a number of pieces of legislation that we have been pushing for years.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "What would you like to see in terms of specific gun control?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "ORGAN: No, I want you to answer this.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "Can I follow-through on the Australia thing?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "Whatever that gun looks like, it's a semiautomatic rifle.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "Allowing, therefore, a clearly deranged son to take them and commit this atrocity?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "Right, it is time.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "It's time for change?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "To get rid of some of these gun laws that cause --", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "Time to do what?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "Look at what has happened, all these attacks this year have occurred where guns are banned.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "To get rid of the gun laws?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "You never let me explain.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "What has that got to do with it?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "-- gun-free zone.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Can I say something?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "Well, I believe those of us who are licensed to carry, are responsible people, shouldn't be prohibited from carrying in schools or other places.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "Here's why, Piers.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "Why on Earth would you want more guns in schools after what happened today?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "It's -- it's impossible to put words to what I really feel.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "What were your feelings?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "You know, I do.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "Do you wish after what happened to you and to Josh that tougher laws had been brought in after that to try and do something about this?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "You know, to be honest, it's heartbreaking.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "I mean, I think the president said we need a meaningful action now.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "What are your views about the debate that will now unfold on this?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "I think in the wake of today, a referendum on guns is needed.", "docId": "121214pmt", "aSentId": 667, "question": "What do you feel today?", "qSentId": 666}]